const apiData = [
  [
    {
      Question: "UNIVAC is",
      Options: [
        "A) Universal Automatic Computer",
        "B) Universal Array Computer",
        "C) Unique Automatic Computer",
        "D) Unvalued Automatic Computer",
      ],
      Answer: "A) Universal Automatic Computer",
    },
  ],

  [
    {
      Question: "The two major types of computer chips are",
      Options: [
        "A) External memory chip",
        "B) Primary memory chip",
        "C) Microprocessor chip",
        "D) Both b and c",
      ],
      Answer: "D) Both b and c",
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      Question:
        "Microprocessors as switching devices are for which generation computers",
      Options: [
        "A) First Generation",
        "B) Second Generation",
        "C) Third Generation",
        "D) Fourth Generation",
      ],
      Answer: "C) Third Generation",
    },
  ],

  [
    {
      Question: "The brain of any computer system is",
      Options: ["A) ALU", "B) Memory", "C) CPU", "D) Control unit"],
      Answer: "C) CPU",
    },
  ],

  [
    {
      Question: "The two kinds of main memory are:",
      Options: [
        "A) Primary and secondary",
        "B) Random and sequential",
        "C) ROM and RAM",
        "D) All of above",
      ],
      Answer: "A) Primary and secondary",
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      Question:
        "A storage area used to store data to compensate for the difference in speed at which the different units can handle data is",
      Options: ["A) Memory", "B) Buffer", "C) Accumulator", "D) Address"],
      Answer: "B) Buffer",
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      Question: "Computer is free from tiresome and boredom. We call it",
      Options: [
        "A) Accuracy",
        "B) Reliability",
        "C) Diligence",
        "D) Versatility",
      ],
      Answer: "C) Diligence",
    },
  ],

  [
    {
      Question: "CD-ROM is a",
      Options: [
        "A) Semiconductor memory",
        "B) Memory register",
        "C) Magnetic memory",
        "D) None of above",
      ],
      Answer: "C) Magnetic memory",
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      Question: "A hybrid computer",
      Options: [
        "A) Resembles digital computer",
        "B) Resembles analogue computer",
        "C) Resembles both a digital and analogue computer",
        "D) None of the above",
      ],
      Answer: "C) Resembles both a digital and analogue computer",
    },
  ],
  [
    {
      Question: "Which type of computers uses the 8-bit code called EBCDIC?",
      Options: [
        "A) Minicomputers",
        "B) Microcomputers",
        "C) Mainframe computers",
        "D) Super computer",
      ],
      Answer: "C) Mainframe computers",
    },
  ],
];

export default apiData;
